<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<news>   
	<newsItem>
		<title><![CDATA[Kobalt Tools 500 at Atlanta Motor Speedway]]></title>
		<body><![CDATA[March 03, 2009 - Joey Logano heads to his home track of Atlanta Motor Speedway (AMS) this weekend for the NASCAR Sprint Cup Series event. Logano grew up racing around AMS, but on the smaller front-stretch oval in Bandoleros and Legends cars.<br><a href="press-releases/news-story_030309.aspx">More >></a>]]></body>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<title><![CDATA[Logano Earns First Career Top-15 Finish in The Home Depot Toyota in Vegas]]></title>
		<body><![CDATA[March 01, 2009 - Joey Logano earned a career-best NASCAR Sprint Cup finish when he drove the No. 20 Home Depot Toyota to a 13th-place finish at Las Vegas Motor Speedway. Logano led a lap and ran in the top 20 most of the race before crossing the finish line in the top 15.<br><a href="press-releases/news-story_030109.aspx">More >></a>]]></body>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<title><![CDATA[Shelby 427 at Las Vegas Motor Speedway]]></title>
		<body><![CDATA[February 25, 2009 - Joey Logano continues his rookie season at another track the 18-year-old has yet to compete on, Las Vegas Motor Speedway (LVMS).  Logano didn't turn 18 until May of 2008, after NASCAR visited the Nevada track.<br><a href="press-releases/news-story_022509.aspx">More >></a>]]></body>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<title><![CDATA[Logano Finishes 26th in The Home Depot Toyota in California]]></title>
		<body><![CDATA[February 22, 2009 - Joey Logano finished 26th in his first NASCAR Sprint Cup Series race at Auto Club Speedway in Fontana, Calif.<br><a href="press-releases/news-story_022209.aspx">More >></a>]]></body>
	</newsItem>
	<newsItem>
		<title><![CDATA[Auto Club 500 at Auto Club Speedway; Fontana, Calif.]]></title>
		<body><![CDATA[February 18, 2009 - Expectations for the weekend: "I can't go into the weekends thinking about expectations. I know I have a lot to learn at these tracks so I need to focus on doing the best that I can."<br><a href="press-releases/news-story_021809.aspx">More >></a>]]></body>
	</newsItem>
</news>